{
  "id": "055-health",
  "title": "Health & Body",
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "skausmas",
      "choices": [
        "pain",
        "health",
        "body",
        "head"
      ],
      "answer": "pain",
      "tts": "skausmas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "galva",
      "choices": [
        "head",
        "arm",
        "leg",
        "hand"
      ],
      "answer": "head",
      "tts": "galva"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "ranką",
      "choices": [
        "hand",
        "leg",
        "foot",
        "head"
      ],
      "answer": "hand",
      "tts": "ranką"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "koja",
      "choices": [
        "leg",
        "arm",
        "hand",
        "head"
      ],
      "answer": "leg",
      "tts": "koja"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "gydytojas",
      "choices": [
        "doctor",
        "nurse",
        "police",
        "teacher"
      ],
      "answer": "doctor",
      "tts": "gydytojas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "skausmas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "galva"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "ranka"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "koja"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "gydytojas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "skausmas",
      "choices": [
        "pain",
        "health",
        "body",
        "head"
      ],
      "answer": "pain",
      "tts": "skausmas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "galva",
      "choices": [
        "head",
        "arm",
        "leg",
        "hand"
      ],
      "answer": "head",
      "tts": "galva"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "ranką",
      "choices": [
        "hand",
        "leg",
        "foot",
        "head"
      ],
      "answer": "hand",
      "tts": "ranką"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "koja",
      "choices": [
        "leg",
        "arm",
        "hand",
        "head"
      ],
      "answer": "leg",
      "tts": "koja"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "gydytojas",
      "choices": [
        "doctor",
        "nurse",
        "police",
        "teacher"
      ],
      "answer": "doctor",
      "tts": "gydytojas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "skausmas"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "galva"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "ranka"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "koja"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "gydytojas"
    }
  ]
}